[A] I would become a subject matter expert.
[A] So let's say for the context of this, I've identified as the InfoFi team,.
[A] I want Monette.
[A] So I'm just going to make the most cracked Monette threads out the gate for free immediately. And I'm just going to start posting that shit on the timeline while I'm trying to reach out to them. In the context of this framework,.
[A] I'm a brilliant educator.
[A] So my content is going to stand out. It's qualitative,.
[A] Not quantitative.
[A] So people are going to notice it.
[A] And then when we're on the call.
[A] Oh, they noticed me from my content because cold emails are probably not going to go anywhere.
[A] Most of it's going to be from they've heard of me from the timeline because my threads are crap.
[A] Look guys,.
[A] I provided you this content for free, but a man's got to eat.
[A] I'm going to provide value first,.
[A] But I want to be paid to create threads for them. And eventually I want to build a product that again,.
[A] Kind of have to start as a volunteer. It sucks.
[A] It feels really gross because you know, the value you're bringing should be paid.
[A] But the issue is they don't they don't know how good you are and they won't know how good you are until you've proven yourself you have to show them and be undeniable.